<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<odoo>
    <data noupdate="0">

        <record id="resfilecategoryreport_lease" model="res.file.category.report" forcecreate="False">
            <field name="name">Lease standard</field>
            <field name="category_id" ref="wua_crm_filemgmt.resfilecategory_lease_file"/>
            <field name="iractreportxml_id" ref="wua_crm_filemgmt.res_file_category_report_lease"/>
            <field name="report_template_start" type="html">
                <p style="text-align: right;">
                    In {% if record.env.user.city %} {{ record.env.user.city }}, {% else %}
                    <span style="color:red;">Not found</span>, {% endif %} a
                    {{ record.env['wua.parcel'].transform_date_to_locale(record.date_file) }}<br/>
                </p>
                <p style="text-align: center;">
                    <b>GATHERED</b>
                    <br/>
                </p>
                <p style="text-align: justify;">
                    ON THE ONE PART, as LESSOR, the community member identified under the heading of Lessor, hereinafter
                    referred to as the <b>Lessor</b> for the purposes of this contract.<br/>
                    <br/>
                    ON THE OTHER PART, as TENANT, the community member identified under the heading of Tenant, hereinafter
                    referred to as the <b>Tenant</b> for the purposes of this contract.<br/>
                    <br/>
                    Both parties agree to the LEASE of the cadastral parcels indicated in the section <b>Involved parcels</b>,
                    and in accordance with the agreements and general conditions described in the WHEREAS section.<br/>
               </p>
            </field>
            <field name="report_template_end" type="html">
                <ul style="list-style-type:none; padding:0; margin:0;">
                    <li><b>I.</b> That both parties intervene in their own name and right.</li>
                    <li><b>II.</b> That both parties mutually recognize the legal capacity necessary to grant this rural lease
                    of the farms described in the section <b>Involved parcels</b>, which they freely agree to in accordance with the
                    general conditions described below.</li>
                </ul>
                <br/>
                <p style="text-align: center;">
                    <b>GENERAL CONDITIONS</b>
                </p>
                <p style="text-align: justify;">
                    <b>1st. Legal regime.</b><br/>
                    This contract is governed by what is expressly agreed by the parties, provided that it does not oppose the Law.
                    In addition, the Civil Code will govern and, failing that, the uses and customs that are applicable.<br/>
                    <br/>
                    <b>2nd. Duration.</b><br/>
                    This contract will last for ........... years.<br/>
                    Once the time has elapsed, the lessee will make possession of the leased properties available to the lessor.<br/>
                    The <b>lessor</b>, in order to recover possession of the property at the end of the contractual term, must reliably
                    notify the lessee one year in advance. Otherwise, if the lessee does not make possession of the leased properties
                    available to the lessor at the end of the term, the contract shall be understood as extended for a period of five
                    years. Such extensions will continue indefinitely until the contract is denounced.<br/>
                    <br/>
                    <b>3rd. Development of the contract.</b><br/>
                    The <b>tenant</b> has the right to determine the type of crop, without prejudice to his obligation to return the property,
                    at the end of the lease, in the state in which it was received and the provisions of the Law on improvements.<br/>
                    <br/>
                    <b>4th. Criteria and formal requirements.</b><br/>
                    This contract may be entered into a public deed at the request of any of the parties, being on the account of the party
                    request the expenses that derive from it.<br/>
                    <br/>
                    <b>5th. Rent.</b><br/>
                    The tenant will pay the lessor an income of............ € per year.<br/>
                    The rent will be updated for each annuity by reference to the annual consumer price index.<br/>
                    The rent will be paid in arrears, within the ............ first days of the month of ......................... ,
                    setting as domicile for payment.................................................. .....................................
                    .......................................
                    <br/>
                    The <b>Lessor</b> agrees to provide the tenant with a receipt for payment.<br/>
                    All amounts to be paid by the <b>Lessor</b> and that by legal provision are chargeable to the <b>Tenan</b> may be demanded by
                    the <b>lessor</b> from the moment they have been paid, stating the concept, amount and provision that authorizes the charge.
                    Failure to pay such amounts will be equivalent to non-payment of rent. The right to pass on will prescribe one year after the
                    payment has been made by the <b>Lessor</b>.<br/>
                    <br/>
                    <b>6th. Insurance contract.</b><br/>
                    The <b>Tenant</b> may insure the normal production of the farm against the normally insurable risks, being able to pass on to
                    the <b>Lessor</b>, from the moment in which he is notified of the arranged insurance, a part of the premium that he saves, in
                    relation to its total amount, the same proportion that exists between the income and the total sum insured.<br/>
                    <br/>
                    <b>7th. Expenses and improvements.</b><br/>
                    The <b>Lessor</b> and the <b>Tenant</b> are obliged to allow the carrying out of the works, repairs and improvements that the
                    other contracting party must or may carry out. Said repairs will be carried out at the time of the year and in the manner that
                    disturbs the least, unless they cannot be deferred.<br/>
                    <br/>
                    <b>8th. Assignment and sublease.</b><br/>
                    The <b>Tenant</b> may not assign or sublease the farm or exploitation without the express consent of the <b>Lessor</b>. This
                    will not be necessary when the assignment or sublease is made in favor of the spouse or one of the lessee's descendants,
                    although the assignment or sublease must be communicated by either party to the lessor within a period of sixty business days
                    from of your celebration. The assignment and sublease will refer to the entire property or exploitation, and will be granted
                    for the entire time remaining in the lease term for a rent that may not exceed the amount agreed between the <b>lessor</b> and
                    the <b>tenant</b>.<br/>
                    <br/>
                    <b>9th. Termination, resolution and rescission of the lease.</b><br/>
                    The lease will end for any of the following reasons:<br/>
                    <span> </span>a) For total loss of the leased thing and for forced expropriation when it is also total. If the loss or
                    expropriation were partial, the lessee may continue with the lease, proportionally reducing the rent. In addition, in case of
                    expropriation, he will be entitled to the compensation that has been set.<br/>
                    <span> </span>b) By expiration of the legal and conventional term and of the extension, if applicable.<br/>
                    <span> </span>c) By mutual agreement of the parties.<br/>
                    <span> </span>d) By unilateral withdrawal of the <b>Tenant</b>, at the end of the agricultural year, having to notify the
                    <b>Lessor</b> one year in advance.<br/>
                    <span> </span>e) Due to the death of the <b>Tenant</b>, the right of their legitimate successors being protected under the terms
                    established in the Law.<br/>
                    <span> </span>f) In leases made in favor of legal persons or community property, from the moment of its extinction.<br/>
                    <span> </span>g) By resolution of the <b>Lessor</b>'s right.<br/>
                    <br/>
                    In addition, it may be resolved at the request of the <b>Lessor</b> for any of the following reasons:<br/>
                    <span> </span>a) Lack of payment of the rent or the amounts assimilated to it.<br/>
                    <span> </span>b) Seriously breaching the obligation to improve or transform the property, to which the <b>Tenant</b> had committed in
                    the contract.<br/>
                    <br/>
                    And for the record, they sign this lease, in duplicate, on the date and place indicated above.
                </p>
            </field>
        </record>

       <record id="resfilecategoryreport_trading" model="res.file.category.report" forcecreate="False">
            <field name="name">Trading standard</field>
            <field name="category_id" ref="wua_crm_filemgmt.resfilecategory_trading_file"/>
            <field name="iractreportxml_id" ref="wua_crm_filemgmt.res_file_category_report_trading"/>
            <field name="report_template_start" type="html">
                <p style="text-align: right;">
                    In {% if record.env.user.city %} {{ record.env.user.city }}, {% else %}
                    <span style="color:red;">Not found</span>, {% endif %} a
                    {{ record.env['wua.parcel'].transform_date_to_locale(record.date_file) }}<br/>
                </p>
                <p style="text-align: center;">
                    <b>GATHERED</b>
                    <br/>
                </p>
                <p style="text-align: justify;">
                    ON THE ONE PART, as SELLER, the community member identified under the heading of Seller, hereinafter referred
                    to as the <b>Seller</b> for the purposes of this contract.<br/>
                    <br/>
                    ON THE OTHER PART, as BUYER, the community member identified under the heading of Buyer, referred to hereinafter
                    and for the purposes of this contract as the <b>Buyer</b>.<br/>
                    <br/>
                    Both parties agree to the TRADING of the cadastral parcles indicated in the section <b>Involved parcels</b>, and
                    in accordance with the agreements and general conditions described in the WHEREAS section.<br/>
               </p>
            </field>
            <field name="report_template_end" type="html">
                <ul style="list-style-type:none; padding:0; margin:0;">
                    <li><b>I.</b> That both parties intervene in their own name and right.</li>
                    <li><b>II.</b> That both parties mutually recognize the legal capacity necessary to grant this rural trading
                    of the farms described in the section <b>Involved parcels</b>, which they freely agree to in accordance with the
                    general conditions described below.</li>
                    <li><b>III.</b> That the <b>Seller</b> is the owner of full ownership of the properties described in the
                    <b>Involved parcels</b> section.</li>
                </ul>
                <br/>
                <p> The rustic properties described in the section <b>Involved parcels</b> are being sold for a <b>value</b> of <b>.........€</b>.</p>
                <br/>
                <p style="text-align: center;">
                    <b>GENERAL CONDITIONS</b>
                </p>
                <p style="text-align: justify;">
                    <b>1st. Trading.</b><br/>
                    That the <b>Seller</b> sells to the <b>Buyer</b> the rustic properties described in the section <b>Involved parcels</b> free of
                    charges and leases, along with all elements thereof that they are accessories and inherent to them.<br/>
                    <br/>
                    <b>2nd. Price.</b><br/>
                    The total price of this sale is ......... €.<br/>
                    <br/>
                    <b>3rd. Object.</b><br/>
                    The object of this contract are the rural properties described in the section <b>Involved parcels</b>. Parcels are sold as certain
                    bodies, free of charges and tenants, and up to date with the payment of contributions, taxes and excise duties, in its current,
                    physical and legal state, known by the parties.<br/>
                    <br/>
                    In this act, the <b>Seller</b> delivers to the <b>Buyer</b>, who receives it, in perfect conditions of use.<br/>
                    <br/>
                    <b>4th. Elevation to public deed and registration in the property registry.</b><br/>
                    The <b>Buyer</b>, may demand the elevation of this contract to the public to request its registration in the corresponding Property
                    Registry. All expenses, taxes and excise duties, which accrue accordingly, including the Plus-Valía Municipal Excise, if any, must be
                    paid in accordance with current legislation.<br/>
                    <br/>
                    <b>5ª. Jurisdiction.</b><br/>
                    The parties, expressly waiving any jurisdiction that may correspond to them, for questions that may arise or actions brought on the
                    interpretation of compliance or non-compliance with what is agreed herein, expressly submit to the Judges and Courts of
                    {% if record.env.user.city %} {{ record.env.user.city }}. {% else %} <span style="color:red;">Not found</span>.{% endif %}<br/>
                    <br/>
                    And for the record, they sign this trading contract, in duplicate, on the date and place indicated above.
                </p>
            </field>
        </record>

       <record id="resfilecategoryreport_complaint" model="res.file.category.report" forcecreate="False">
            <field name="name">Complaint standard</field>
            <field name="category_id" ref="wua_crm_filemgmt.resfilecategory_complaint_file"/>
            <field name="iractreportxml_id" ref="wua_crm_filemgmt.res_file_category_report_complaint"/>
            <field name="report_template_start" type="html">
                <p style="text-align: right;">
                    In {% if record.env.user.city %} {{ record.env.user.city }}, {% else %}
                    <span style="color:red;">Not found</span>, {% endif %} a
                    {{ record.env['wua.parcel'].transform_date_to_locale(record.date_file) }}<br/>
                </p>
            </field>
            <field name="report_template_end" type="html">
                <p><i>Free text</i></p>
            </field>
        </record>

       <record id="resfilecategoryreport_custom" model="res.file.category.report" forcecreate="False">
            <field name="name">Custom standard (empty)</field>
            <field name="category_id" ref="crm_filemgmt.resfilecategory_internal_file"/>
            <field name="iractreportxml_id" ref="wua_crm_filemgmt.res_file_category_report_custom"/>
            <field name="report_template_start" type="html">
                <p><i>Free text</i></p>
            </field>
            <field name="report_template_end" type="html">
                <p><i>Free text</i></p>
            </field>
        </record>

    </data>
</odoo>